"Costa Rica","COUNTRY"
"Brazil","COUNTRY"
"Russia","COUNTRY"
"Saya Suka Video","ORGANIZATION"
"UN","ORGANIZATION"
"Argentina","COUNTRY"
"Ahmed Musa","PERSON"
"attack","CAUSE_OF_DEATH"
"Roger Milla","PERSON"
"African","NATIONALITY"
"Nalex Iwobi","PERSON"
"Nigeria","COUNTRY"
"Iceland","COUNTRY"
"John Obi Mikel","PERSON"
"his","PERSON"
"Uzoho","PERSON"
"midfielder","TITLE"
"Sigurdsson","PERSON"
"Nvar","PERSON"
"he","PERSON"
"referee","TITLE"
"Nahmed Musa","PERSON"
"Rohr Gernot","PERSON"
"coach","TITLE"
"second","TITLE"
"He","PERSON"
"HIS","PERSON"
"goalkeeper","TITLE"
"SECOND","TITLE"
"Gislason","PERSON"
"Ragnar Sigurdsson","PERSON"
"Sverrir Ingason","PERSON"
"FIFA","ORGANIZATION"
"Ahmed Musa Bags Brace","PERSON"
"Gylfi Sigurdsson","PERSON"
"His","PERSON"
"Hannes Halldorsson","PERSON"
"Rurik Gislason","PERSON"
"Victor Moses","PERSON"
"Ndidi","PERSON"
"Halldorsson","PERSON"
"Musa","PERSON"
"Moses","PERSON"
"Oghenekaro Etebo","PERSON"
"Second","TITLE"
"BIRKIR BJARNASON","PERSON"
"defender","TITLE"
"Birkir Bjarnason","PERSON"
"Francis Uzoho","PERSON"
"ICELAND","COUNTRY"
"Wilfred NDIDI","PERSON"
"Bjarnason","PERSON"
"Nnigeria","LOCATION"
"Algeria","COUNTRY"
"South Korea","COUNTRY"
"Brazilian","NATIONALITY"
"Manchester United","ORGANIZATION"
"opener","TITLE"
"Gianni Infantino","PERSON"
"President","TITLE"
"Finnbogason","PERSON"
"Mikel","PERSON"
"striker","TITLE"
"Lionel Messi","PERSON"
"Uzoho","LOCATION"
"Mueller","PERSON"
"Christopher Steele","PERSON"
"Abramovich","PERSON"
"Nbrazil","ORGANIZATION"
"FIFA RUSSIA","ORGANIZATION"
"RUSSIA","COUNTRY"
"sticker","TITLE"
"NIGERIA","COUNTRY"
"India","COUNTRY"
"Egyptian","NATIONALITY"
"Neymar","PERSON"
"Coutinho","PERSON"
"@NEYMARJR","ORGANIZATION"
"Petersburg","CITY"
"St.","LOCATION"
"Telemundo","ORGANIZATION"
"Argentina-Croatia","ORGANIZATION"
"FIFA World Cup Russia","ORGANIZATION"
"Switzerland","COUNTRY"
"Serbia","COUNTRY"
"Kieran Cooke","PERSON"
"NHERE","ORGANIZATION"
"Nintendo","ORGANIZATION"
"Chris Eddy","PERSON"
"investment analyst","TITLE"
"Painter","TITLE"
"Italian","NATIONALITY"
"painter","TITLE"
"NSOTB","ORGANIZATION"
"guide","TITLE"
"La","STATE_OR_PROVINCE"
"Fox","ORGANIZATION"
"fever","CAUSE_OF_DEATH"
"Indian","NATIONALITY"
"Messi","PERSON"
"Ghana","COUNTRY"
"GFA","ORGANIZATION"
"Denmark","COUNTRY"
"Australia","COUNTRY"
"Fort Myers","PERSON"
"Bonita Springs","CITY"
"Naples","CITY"
"Cape Coral","CITY"
"Peru","COUNTRY"
"France","COUNTRY"
"Nike","ORGANIZATION"
"Telemart","LOCATION"
"Speaker","TITLE"
"FIFA World Cup & Order","ORGANIZATION"
"FIFA World Cup","ORGANIZATION"
"FIFA World","ORGANIZATION"
"UEFA","ORGANIZATION"
"Saudi Arabia","COUNTRY"
"pirate","TITLE"
"sports minister","TITLE"
"Beoutq","PERSON"
"Turki","PERSON"
"president","TITLE"
"Aleksander","PERSON"
"Panama","COUNTRY"
"British","NATIONALITY"
"Russian","NATIONALITY"
"EU","ORGANIZATION"
"U.S.","COUNTRY"
"Katsap","PERSON"
"NFIFA","ORGANIZATION"
"Jose Ramirez Barreto","PERSON"
"Salah","PERSON"
"Neymar","LOCATION"
"MESSI","PERSON"
"Maradona","PERSON"
"Rishi Tej","PERSON"
"Tamil Nadu","LOCATION"
"her","PERSON"
"FIFA World Cup - Times of India","ORGANIZATION"
"Sweden","COUNTRY"
"Germany","COUNTRY"
"Nbrazil","PERSON"
"Times of India","ORGANIZATION"
"Nnigeria","ORGANIZATION"
"US","LOCATION"
"MÉXICO","ORGANIZATION"
"fall","CAUSE_OF_DEATH"
"FIFA World Cup Group E.","ORGANIZATION"
"Bjorn Kuipers","PERSON"
"Captain","TITLE"
"Portugal","COUNTRY"
"Cristiano Ronaldo","PERSON"
"K International","ORGANIZATION"
"FIFA World Cup & Game","ORGANIZATION"
"Tunisia","COUNTRY"
"England","COUNTRY"
"Bafana Bafana","PERSON"
"Asia","CITY"
"Africa","LOCATION"
"header","TITLE"
"Morocco","COUNTRY"
"Iceland - Musa","ORGANIZATION"
"Argentina","ORGANIZATION"
"Croatia","COUNTRY"
"CROATIA","COUNTRY"
"Nargentina","ORGANIZATION"
"Modric","PERSON"
"Belgium","COUNTRY"
"Panama","ORGANIZATION"
"McDonald","ORGANIZATION"
"Chinese","NATIONALITY"
"Spain","COUNTRY"
"Austria","COUNTRY"
"Korea","COUNTRY"
"Mexico","ORGANIZATION"
"Republic","LOCATION"
"Adidas","ORGANIZATION"
"Putin","PERSON"
"Saya","PERSON"
"New Post","ORGANIZATION"
"Elliott Bennett","PERSON"
"Blackburn Rovers","ORGANIZATION"
"OPENCULTURE","PERSON"
"FBI","ORGANIZATION"
"Nyt","ORGANIZATION"
"UK","COUNTRY"
"Moscow","CITY"
"Koop","PERSON"
"New York Times","ORGANIZATION"
"Michael Barbaro","PERSON"
"fire","CAUSE_OF_DEATH"
"Volgograd","CITY"
"Arena","LOCATION"
"Referee","TITLE"
"Wilfred Ndidi","PERSON"
"Auckland","CITY"
"Memories Inspiring Milinkovic-Savic","LOCATION"
"Guerrero","CITY"
"Lewandowski","PERSON"
"Adidas Football","ORGANIZATION"
"El Hadary","LOCATION"
"Malaysia","COUNTRY"
"FIFA World Cup Russia™ - news - Ir Iran","ORGANIZATION"
"Republic -","LOCATION"
"Quaresma","PERSON"
"Uruguay","COUNTRY"
"Yerry Mina","PERSON"
"Philippe Coutinho","PERSON"
"El Hadary","PERSON"
"Turns Neymar","LOCATION"
"LGBT Sport Federation","ORGANIZATION"
"Alexander Agapov","PERSON"
"American Airlines","ORGANIZATION"
"Poland","COUNTRY"
"Senegal","COUNTRY"
"Sampaoli","PERSON"
"reporter","TITLE"
"ASSAULT","CRIMINAL_CHARGE"
"CBC","ORGANIZATION"
"Creston","CITY"
"BC","STATE_OR_PROVINCE"
"Ronaldo","PERSON"
"FIFA World Cup, Group Stage","ORGANIZATION"
"Madison Bumgarner","PERSON"
"Giants","ORGANIZATION"
"Wide Receiver","TITLE"
"Mike","PERSON"
"Robertson","PERSON"
"OKC","LOCATION"
"Russell Westbrook","PERSON"
"James Harden","PERSON"
"Kevin Durant","PERSON"
"Gant","PERSON"
"Cardinals","ORGANIZATION"
"Norris","PERSON"
"Cle M Clevinger","PERSON"
"Indians","ORGANIZATION"
"Jeanie Buss","PERSON"
"Lakers","ORGANIZATION"
"MCGREGOR","PERSON"
"Cormier","PERSON"
"Jon Jones","PERSON"
"Brock Lesnar","PERSON"
"McGregor","PERSON"
"Wilder","PERSON"
"Joshua","PERSON"
"NBA","ORGANIZATION"
"Casey","PERSON"
"Prince","PERSON"
"Braves","ORGANIZATION"
"Floro","PERSON"
"Jackson","PERSON"
"Lonzo Ball","PERSON"
"Kyle Kuzma","PERSON"
"Lonzo BALLHTTP","PERSON"
"Russ","PERSON"
"Mitchell","PERSON"
"Simmons","PERSON"
"Coach","TITLE"
"Dwane Casey","PERSON"
"United States","COUNTRY"
"Hou J verlander","PERSON"
"TOR J HAPP","PERSON"
"Astros","ORGANIZATION"
"Blue Jays","ORGANIZATION"
"Ballin","PERSON"
"Rockets","ORGANIZATION"
"Anthony Davis","PERSON"
"NBA MVP","ORGANIZATION"
"Cavaliers","ORGANIZATION"
"Lebron James","PERSON"
"Gobert","PERSON"
"Cubs","ORGANIZATION"
"Anthony Davishttp","PERSON"
"Issa","PERSON"
"","Tamil Nadu#LOCATION"
"Nclick","PERSON"
"Ahmed Musa Great Volley","PERSON"
